Nehal Mavchy

Lead - Trans processing

\square	mavchynehal@gmail.co
	m





A competent professional, completed Post Graduate Degree in MBA from Pune University in 2014; with over 8 years of professional experience in Client management/service, Process improvement/excellence, Quality assurance, Salesforce, SAP, Internal Audits

Profile Summary

I am a seasoned working professional with a total of 8 years work experience, currently associated with Sutherland global services as a Lead-Trans processing (US/Canada support). My current role includes working on Order management, Material code management, Proposal creation, coordinating with the client through email, call & chat, understanding the requirements & making sure to complete assigned work within stipulated period of time to meet the deadlines/SLA.

Education

2014, Full Time

MBA/PGDM, Pune University,

2012, Full Time

B.Sc, Pune University,

2009

12th, Madhya Pradesh, English, 60-64.9%

2007

10th, Madhya Pradesh, English, 75-79.9%

Work Experience

2017 - Present

Lead - Trans processing

Sutherland Global Services

- Handled Order management, Proposal creation, Material code management, Internal Audits.
- Handling data base for US/ CANADA customers, order management and proposal creations.
- Reviewed existing processes, and spearheaded the implementation of systems aimed at enhancing process and operational efficiency of the organization, worked on continuous improvement.
- Quickly respond to the calls, web cases, emails and chats with the requestor to get resolution and deliver a high level of service and to ensure quality working and customer satisfaction.
- Formulated need-based business strategies for maximizing profitability & revenue generation & realizing organizational goals.
- Key Contributor to order management Process Management Team ensuring that the incoming transactions are validated and booked in the systems.

- Analysed gaps and spearheaded process improvement ideas to minimize the error and process time.
- Developed formal plans for continuous improvement and measurement in terms of management goals and objectives, customer service delivery, and customer relationships.
- Provides customer support at a specialist level, acting as the "knowledge base" of information across the Order Management functions and sharing knowledge within team and helping to get order uploaded.
- Established in-house quality standards, ensuring high-quality deliverables while adhering to the SLAs.
- · Identifeed needs for training and conducting regular training sessions for new joinees as well as team members
- Responsible for creating order forms for customers as per client requirements.
- Train new people in team for Proposal creation process.
- Prepare checklist related to order booking and proposals to set internal audit parameters.
- Auditing cases (Internally) on daily basis to ensure quality.
- Maintain and audit data of all the cases processed by team members.
- Handling GRA (Global Revenue Assurance) revenue recognition process.
- · Performing validation of documents and prepare packages related to revenue based on orders booked.
- Work with client to get approvals for the packages sent on daily basis in order to recognize revenue for the company.
- Working as a member of the Avaya Services Offer team to manage a catalog of over 6,000 SAP material codes.
- Working with internal teams (Ops, Finance, IT, SAP Admin, Provisioning) to meet processing deadlines for offer launch dates
- Promoting operational excellence, customer service, problem solving, project management skills and teamwork.
- Managing the SAP Material Code creation and maintenance process for Avaya Professional Services.
- Acting as prime for SAP Master Data Governance (MDG) tool for MC creation.
- · Maintaining the Avaya Professional Services Catalog.
- Working with internal teams to get material codes ready for Offer launch dates.
- Creating ROC (Revenue Office Council) files based on the given spreadsheets.
- Ability to handle work independently and proactively with good problem-solving skills.
- · Acting as Liaison and SME on material code attributes within Avaya?s other Business Units.
- Creating job aids regarding material code information for the Offer Management Team.
- Tracking, auditing, and submitting MC creation requests to MD Team.
- Creating ROC slides on behalf of offer managers and submit to ROC for approval and weekly update to offer managers of ROC approval by packages.
- Assisting team with SAP related inquiries associated with Material Code Attributes.

Application used for Order Management, Proposal creation, Material code creation:

- ? SFDC (Salesforce dot com)
- ? SAP (12P)
- ? SAP MDG (MP4)
- ? Microsoft Outlook
- ? Microsoft Teams
- ? Avaya one source, Avaya Store
- ? Avaya (Spaces)
- ? Pro Services Now (PSN)
- ? Qvidian (Proposal Creation)

2016 - 2017

Team Lead- Recruitment

Jobs Cruze Consultancy Services

- Worked as a Team Lead- Recruitment (BFSI).
- Team size handled (8-10 recruiters)
- Sourcing recruiters through portals to fill team gap & schedule interviews of shortlisted candidates.
- · Conducting training session for new joiners.
- Maintain daily reports, work sheet of team & formulate weekly & monthly plans for team.
- Preparing new plans and daily targets of team, drive & motivate them to get the work done.
- To develop new ideas, plans for the betterment of team & organization and daily reporting to the manager.
- · Attend monthly meetings with client companies to build & maintain relationship with clients.
- Proper follow-ups with the clients for selection & joining of candidates.

2015 - 2016

Senior HR Executive

Fundatastic Works Pvt. Ltd.

- Handled recruitment through portals, social media and references.
- Worked on profile screening, Interview scheduling, Arranging interviews, Proper follow-ups, On-boarding formalities, Offer generation, Documentation of selected candidates.
- Prepared new plans, daily targets of employees & monthly reports for clients.
- Responsible for record keeping (Attendance, Leave), preparing salaries, incentives, performance appraisals of

employees.

- Reporting to the manager and director on daily basis & assist other HR?s.
- Handled corporate permissions, events & also present and participate in the fundraising events.
- Prepared a monthly meeting schedule with potential donors.
- Developed new ideas, plans for the betterment of organization.

Key Skills

internal audit service delivery process improvement customer process excellence service client management service **Material Management** Client **Team Management** excellence Handling **Process Management Client Relationship Order Management** Sales Order Management **Processing Client Support Process** specialist

Language

English Hindi Marathi Expert Expert Proficient

Personal Details

Date of Birth

Gender

Marital Status

19th September 1991

Female

Single / Unmarried

Address

NIBM Road, Pune